Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Look. I think we should handle this
like we always do.
-What are the pros. what are the cons?
-Okay.
Well. pro. it's the ultimate get-out
for family gatherings.
"It's killing me
to not come to your wedding.
but I'm just super busy
running the country right now."
-Con.
-Hmm.
Sylvie'll have a camera
pointed in her face
every time she goes out.
Mmm.
Pro.
-You can change the world.
-Mmm.
You know. like. really help people.
Yeah.
That's why you went into politics
in the first place.
Mmm.
Con.
-Mmm?
-I'm shit on TV.
Mmm… yeah. That's true.
Oh!
You know.
if you threw your hat in the ring
with the party.
you'd be the instant front-runner.
And then you'd smash it
in a general election.
I… I just don't want
anything to damage this.
You know. the three of us.
If it ever comes down to a choice.
you'll make the right one.
Yeah.
♪ Oh. oh. do you shiver? ♪
♪ Shiver now. skies ablaze ♪
♪ I'm gonna bring you down ♪
♪ I said. "Where?" ♪
♪ "Where you gonna run?" ♪
♪ On the other side. overloaded gun ♪
♪ I need to know ♪
♪ Can you feel the heat now? ♪
♪ Oh. oh. oh. now. now ♪
♪ Hey. now. now. oh. now. now ♪
♪ Hey. now. oh. now. now ♪
♪ Oh-oh. oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey. now. now. oh. now. now ♪
♪ Hey. now. oh. now. now ♪
♪ Oh-oh. oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey. now. now. oh. now. now ♪
Congratulations
and welcome to Downing Street.
Prime Minister.
Thank you.
Order!
Order. order. order. order!
Question to the prime minister.
Oliver Bahrami.
Thank you. Mr. Speaker.
Eight months ago.
the prime minister won office
with a promise to fix
our NHS and social care system
by gutting the military to pay for it.
Now. thanks to the right honorable lady.
you can fit the entire British Army
into Wembley Stadium.
And still have room for the away fans
of her beloved Oldham FC.
Meanwhile… meanwhile. on her watch.
the National Health Service
faces an acute supply crisis
of vital cancer drugs
and other medications.
pushing thousands of people
to the brink of desperation and death.
So isn't it time she finally apologized
for utterly failing the British people?
As I discussed
with Léopold when I visited last week.
these people are doctors
from Médecins Sans Frontières.
They're here to offer free vaccinations
to the kids
and health checks for everyone!
Men. women. children. everyone!
-Hi. Bonjour.
-Oui.
Bonjour.
We are now
weeks into this crisis.
yet the government's so-called strategy
seems to amount to little more
than going cap in hand to the French.
Today. as the prime minister begins
this critical summit
with President Toussaint.
the public needs real assurances
that we are not walking
into these talks naked.
I'm confused. Mr. Speaker.
I thought the right honorable gentleman
wanted a deal.
Oh. well. he's nodding. Good.
Well. let me explain what that means.
Grit. compromise. not selling out
or accepting anything less
than what our people need.
Every week. we play the same game.
I'm supposed to blame his party
for years of underinvestment in the NHS.
he fires back. and around we go. so…
why don't we try being honest for once?
Hmm.
I will end this shortage.
Nothing will distract me from that.
Your PMQs statement is trending.
Expectations around this summit
were already sky-high.
Now you've gone on record
that the French are the answer.
We'd better get a result. then.
Her car's in Trafalgar Square.
She's three minutes out.
I need to get changed.
So I read your update
on the SOS Méditerranée.
They've confirmed another 12 cases
of Ebola.
It brings the total to 79.
They're being treated on board for now.
-It's just awful.
-But potentially useful.
Look.
even if Toussaint wanted to.
she can't afford
to bring a boatload of refugees
and park it on French soil
six weeks out
from a presidential election.
No. but we could.
in return for the medication we need.
I thought you'd be happier.
About using people fleeing persecution
to our advantage?
-Thrilled.
-We can't give this issue away.
Ready?
Hair? Makeup?
No. I'm fine. but you knock yourself out.
You have to apologize
for the hot-mic incident.
Incident? Is that really
what we're calling it now?
To quote. "Toussaint is a handmaiden
to the hard right."
I'm not apologizing
for her reelection campaign.
What happened to the greeting I learned?
The Foreign Office felt this language
was more… What's the word? Neutral.
Hold on.
Let's go.
Prime Minister!
Madam President.
just one question for you.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
On behalf
of the British people.
I am honored to welcome you
to Downing Street.
-No. that's all I've got.
-Oh.
That's 15 words more
than your predecessor managed.
Right.
You wouldn't believe
the conversations we had
about how long
I should be shaking your hand.
-I hope that was okay for you.
-Yes. it's fine.
Mm-hm.
I could learn a thing or two from you
about the photographers. though.
I think. with you.
it's all about the face muscles.
You should avoid tense expressions.
Okay. I'll bear that in mind.
Ahem. Is your husband not joining us?
I didn't want him
to feel like a spare part.
I know yours is. uh… away working.
Come on. everybody.
The doctors are ready.
This way. Come closer to the tent.
Allez. allez. allez.
You can go now.
-We're not armed!
-Allez!
-Okay.
-Listen. Listen!
-We're here to help!
-Noah. keep your mouth shut!
We work for Médecins Sans Frontières.
Attendez. s'il vous plaît!
S'il vous plaît!
-No. leave him alone!
-No. Maya. Don't move.
-Don't move.
-Please. Please.
Sh! Sh.
Oh my goodness.
Goodness. that's… beautiful.
A replica of
the Field of the Cloth of Gold.
a summit in the 16th century
between Henry VIII
and King François I de France.
They held it in the hopes
of increasing the bonds of friendship
between both countries.
Yes. I have heard of that.
but the kings. they wrestled. didn't they?
Yes.
Henry lost.
Uh. Madam President.
Prime Minister?
-This is very thoughtful. Thank you.
-You're welcome. Ahem.
Let's adjourn to the next room.
-Water?
-Yes. please.
Non. merci.
Ahem.
I'd like to apologize for my comments
that were made public.
"A handmaiden to the hard right."
Mmm. I actually found it quite amusing.
Liberal outrage.
Well. you can't deny that
your positions have radically changed.
The world has changed.
I'm listening to my people.
You're listening to extremists.
Ah. I'm appealing to a silent majority
who values national identity.
just like your people chose to do.
Even if it risks destabilizing a country?
I'm not the one struggling
to preserve the unity. well-being.
and basic health of my people.
Look.
We need your help with our NHS crisis.
and you need ours
with your immigration problem.
Our problem is caused by the UK.
Your border security is soft.
That's the only reason
why people risk crossing the Channel.
You want us to better police our borders?
No. I want to police them for you.
The president is requesting French troops
be posted on British soil
to deter the flow of migrants.
The French people need to feel
that this border is safe.
I'm willing to supply the manpower
to do it.
On sovereign soil of the United Kingdom?
No.
The deal that's on the table
is a stable supply of cancer drugs
and other medications from France
in return for the UK taking in
and treating the people
on board the SOS Méditerranée.
The people on board that boat
are of no interest to me.
You can't mean that.
Well. we've made a start. Perhaps
we should revisit this after lunch.
Wow.
Ma'am. She's back.
♪ Thank you for your patience. baby ♪
♪ Now to let a little
Old-fashioned heartbreak in my life ♪
♪ To keep me occupied… ♪
Sylvie?
Jess's dad called me.
You lied to me.
You told me you were going to Jess's.
not getting drunk in central London.
We weren't making any trouble.
One photograph of you doing something
stupid will stay with you forever.
Don't you think I know that?
I'm upset about Granddad. too.
Sylvie. but this is a big year for you.
You've got your exams. college.
I need to be able to trust you.
-Can I see him?
-Yes. maybe tonight.
Are you listening to me? This is serious.
Can I at least have my phone?
Ayesha took it.
♪ To keep me occupied… ♪
Stay off social media.
-Am I on the news?
-No.
I think we dodged that bullet. Just.
Wish Dad was here.
Well. so do I. sweetheart.
He'll call us later.
when he's done for the day.
Sorry. Prime Minister. but I need you
for the sports initiative photo op.
wearing either these or these?
Uh. your choice.
Let me ask my focus group.
Thank you.
Yes?
So. according to our friend Wiki.
Toussaint played point guard
at university.
which means I'm about to have
my arse handed to me.
Is there any reason why we didn't choose
a sport I'm vaguely familiar with?
I could've crushed her at table tennis.
What's wrong?
Thirty minutes ago.
a Médecins Sans Frontières Jeep was found
abandoned in Oyapock. French Guiana.
A translator is dead.
Alex and three other British doctors
are missing.
Prime Minister. it's our belief
your husband has been abducted.
No.
You should take a moment.
Has anyone claimed responsibility?
Not as yet. It's the first incident
we've had in the region.
It's why there was
no additional protection for Alex.
Have we any idea why they were taken?
It's usually about money. but we are
yet to receive a ransom request.
Are we running rescue scenarios?
We don't have resources in the region
to effect an immediate response.
But the French do. It's their territory.
Do they know about it yet?
I don't think so.
How dangerous is it
to trust Toussaint with this?
It could put you in a weaker position
for the negotiations if you ask for help.
But when they do find out about it.
the question will soon become
why we kept it secret from them.
so maybe we… we… we get in front of this.
Fuck.
Either way.
I think we should assemble the Cabinet.
-We have to keep this need-to-know.
-Prime Minister. I strongly advise--
This'll leak within minutes
if we share this with them.
There are people who would jump at
the opportunity to take advantage of this.
-There is a protocol to follow--
-I said no.
You can brief Ayesha and Zadie.
and Tristan can run point with MI6.
but that's as wide as we go
with this for now.
so just keep Toussaint busy while
I figure out how to tell my daughter.
Is it Granddad?
It's a video. From Dad.
Why does he look like that?
Mum? Mum!
-Ayesha!
-Mum!
-What's going on?
-I need you to listen to me.
We think your dad and his team
may have been abducted.
-We're trying to locate them.
-Why? They're just doctors.
We don't know.
We're gonna do everything we can.
-I'm sorry. Get that to MI6. A video.
-I wanna see him. Give it back!
-It needs analyzing. It's Alex. Shh!
-Let me see it! Give it back!
We need to let them watch it first. Okay?
Come here. come here. come here.
Come here. Sh. Shh.
Not letting that boat
dock in Calais is leading the news.
It's a perfect wedge issue for us.
Great. Next time. you can come
and get spat at with me.
They must have missed that one
off our wedding vows.
No. no. I am more use here
running your campaign.
I have to go.
Shame on you!
Shame on you! Shame on you!
Your stepson is part of the protest.
Shame on you!
Yes. sweetie.
Daddy's going to do bedtime
for the next few nights.
but I'll send you little videos.
Yes. yes. of the big black door.
Big. big kisses.
Mummy loves you very much. Bye.
-Adrienne.
-Good location.
-Great optics.
-Mmm.
Voilà.
-Where's Dalton?
-She'll be right along.
She has business to attend to.
I seriously can't understand why she would
ever consider getting rid of you.
Unless the rumors are not true.
Well.
I was her predecessor's appointment.
so it's perfectly possible
she'd want to bring in new blood.
It's entirely her prerogative.
Just looking at that photographer.
Nice big smiles. Thank you.
I called…
Police escort's standing by to…
I'm going to need the president
back at Downing Street.
Will you be…
-This way. please.
-Thank you.
What is that?
A transcript of a video
you're about to watch.
It concerns a live hostage situation
in French Guiana.
Play it.
Is that…
Yes.
"The path of least resistance
is the easiest to walk."
"It takes no imagination or ingenuity."
Read it out loud.
Go on.
Read!
"You need
to take that path now. Abigail."
"You need to resign as prime minister
by 1:00pm GMT tomorrow."
"Then we will release
Doctors Jacobs. Odari. Lambert. and me."
"If you fail to comply
with this simple request.
then one of us will die.
and we'll try again."
"Don't resist the path."
I'm so sorry. Abigail.
We have 22 hours to respond.
Do we have any intel
that could identify who the captors are?
Not at present. ma'am. Our man
on the ground in Venezuela is on the move.
One man? You weren't kidding
about gutting the military.
Obviously. I've taken a risk
sharing this with you.
but I'm being completely transparent.
You should know
I have no intention of resigning.
but this is French territory.
so I'll need you to deploy your military
and bring him home.
Let's work with the local police
and our networks on the ground
to locate the kidnappers.
Once we have a location.
we'll deploy the Légion étrangère.
We'll go in hard and fast.
We'll bring your husband back.
Thank you.
In the meantime.
you have a press conference
starting in six minutes.
Cancel it.
Any deviation from our planned events
will get people talking.
and that could put Alex and the others
in more jeopardy.
I agree.
You sure you're up to this?
Yes.
Before we start. I'd like to offer
an apology to President Toussaint.
A few months ago at a conference in Delhi.
I made a private comment
over an open microphone.
which was unhelpful and ungenerous.
President Toussaint is trying to win
a second mandate from her people.
and it's easy to stand on the sidelines
and judge her for that.
-I was wrong.
-Madam President!
What do you think of this apology?
Simon Kingsley. The Times.
President Toussaint.
the UK is nearly a month
into a medicine supply chain crisis
that has been causing a shortage
in lifesaving cancer drugs
and a range of medications in the UK.
Our government seems unable
to help the British people. Will you?
A teacher once told me that
the famous French hatred of the British
is all for show.
We despise you out loud.
but we know what we owe you.
We go a long way back. our two nations.
but our bond requires something active
from both of us to keep it in place.
That's why I'm pleased to announce.
as a sign of good faith.
Prime Minister Dalton has agreed
to let the SOS Méditerranée dock
in the UK.
in order for the refugees on board
to be treated and housed here.
I'm confident that this gesture will prove
to be the icebreaker that we both need.
-What the fuck?
-Careful. Your mic might be on.
You're using this situation
to play me. You…
Putting politics aside.
even on a basic fucking human level--
On a human level.
I feel for you and your daughter. Abigail.
As for putting politics aside.
if you wanted your husband back.
you could've made that choice.
No. We don't give in to terrorists.
Yeah. we always say that.
but you could. You absolutely could.
But you won't because you don't want
to give up your power. At least admit it.
I'm the last person on earth
who's going to judge you for that.
So taking in that boat
is the cost of bringing Alex back?
You told me
you didn't even care about those people.
No. I told you they weren't of interest
to me as part of the deal.
Even though you were more than happy
to use them as bargaining chips. I wasn't.
Listen. I'm going to help you
bring your husband back.
but when he's home. you're gonna
have to give me what I came here for.
French border forces on UK soil.
I can't lose this election. Abigail.
See you tonight.
I am gonna bring your dad home.
How?
I'll find a way.
What do they even want?
It's complicated.
Mum. I know there are times
when you can't tell me stuff.
This isn't one of them.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to him.
You have to believe that.
Yeah.
I don't think your granddad
can handle this right now.
So we won't tell him.
He always sees right through me.
Granddad!
Oh!
I know.
Last thing you need is me dying
in the middle of your summit.
-You're not dying.
-Only because you won't let me.
Huh.
Oh. what's this? Contraband?
-Cheese and pickle.
-Ooh!
Right. put it in my drawer.
I'll have it later
when they're not looking. eh?
Hey.
What's going on?
-What's happened?
-Nothing.
Come on. You're a terrible poker player.
It's my fault. actually.
I got in a bit of trouble
for getting drunk with my mate.
-Sylvie Jane!
-I know. it was stupid.
I won't do it again.
Yes. you will.
Listen. you've got to be smart.
I know it seems unfair.
but normal rules. they don't apply to us.
Not anymore.
Right.
Crack open the Scrabble.
I'll whip you both.
One quick game.
I have to go back for a reception.
Oh. la-di-da!
Shall we?
-Madame?
-Good evening. Madame.
-Bonsoir!
-Hello.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. ma'am. Thank you.
Thank you!
-Did we find the doctors?
-Not yet.
Let me know
as soon as they've been located.
Yes. of course.
And the polling
I asked for after the press conference?
You'll have it in a few hours.
Forcing Dalton to take the migrants
on British soil
was a masterstroke. Madam President.
Merci.
-Has Matheo arrived?
-Yes. he's here.
He brought his girlfriend.
Hmm.
Hey.
-Hey.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-It's just your average Thursday night.
-Right?
-Yeah. Yeah. Don't be nervous.
Fuck 'em.
They're lucky to have us. honestly.
You look amazing.
There you are.
How are you? Good suit.
This is Saskia.
Such a pleasure to meet you.
Madam President.
And you.
I'm just sorry I wasn't better prepared.
I usually have a briefing memo
put together for Matheo's plus ones.
She's joking.
Where did you find this one?
It's serious between us.
You should try and be a little nicer.
I should go. See you inside.
-Lovely meeting you. Saskia.
-Mm-hmm. You too.
Wow. um… She's intimidating.
-What did she say?
-She liked your dress.
Hey. Hey.
They'll be putting a rescue together.
It's gonna be all right.
Uh. Ambassador…
Pleasure to meet you.
And you.
Thank you.
What is it you do for pleasure?
For joy? If you don't mind me asking.
Compulsive masturbation.
Online poker.
Before bed or in the night.
Away from everyone and their noise.
I don't know if it brings me joy.
but it clears my head.
We're never alone.
and yet it is so fucking lonely.
He'll be home soon.
-Yeah.
-Take it till I get back.
Excuse me.
We've located the doctors.
-Did she leave already?
-No. she's in the bathroom.
-Why did you invite me here?
-Why did you come?
To thank you
for helping save those people on the boat.
Oh. You should be thanking Abigail Dalton.
-I'll introduce you.
-It was your idea.
I saw the press conference.
I know how you operate.
The woman I remember.
the one I campaigned for.
she believed in positive change.
Don't romanticize me.
I always did the right thing politically.
Mmm. Like marrying my old man?
-He understands the challenge. the game.
-Mmm.
It doesn't hurt that he owns
a news channel and two papers though.
Now he's pushing you
to the right.
They all are.
You're better than this.
Stop with the protests.
If a photographer had seen you.
the stepson of the president…
Sorry. but they need you.
Mmm.
Our agent made it
into French Guiana two hours ago.
He used a local contact to track
the doctors to an abandoned compound.
Does he get
a knighthood for that?
No. but I'll name a bloody bridge
after him.
I think they're bringing them out.
-What's his name?
-Thomas Mercer.
Thomas. this is Abigail Dalton.
-Do you see him?
-Negative. ma'am. Not yet.
Ah. here we go.
They're getting ready to transport them.
-Where's backup?
-Support is incoming.
We're running facial recognition
to confirm IDs first.
That's a positive identification
on Doctors Lambert and Jacobs.
-And one more. Dr. Odari.
-And what about Alex?
Oh God. That's him. How far are your men?
We are two minutes out.
We just need the order. Madam President?
Vivienne. give the order.
What's the matter?
Hey. Easy. Easy.
Jesus. What are you waiting for?
Your… your troops are on
a fucking chopper. Give the order!
-Abort.
-What?
You… you can't do that.
Abort the mission.
Abort mission. Abort mission.
-They're moving out.
-Uh. stay on them.
Copy. Over.
-Give us the room? Give us the room!
-Yes. ma'am.
Why are you changing your mind?
What's happened?
Look. if you won't help me
bring Alex back. then… then who will?
-What am I supposed to tell my daughter?
-Tell her you're gonna have to resign.
That's the only way to get him back.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org